let questions = [
    {   // QUESTION #1
        question: "Where was Alexander Hamilton born?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Scottland",
        choiceB: "Wales",
        choiceC: "New York",
        choiceD: "The Caribbean",
        correct: "D"
    }, { // QUESTION #2
        question: "When living in The Caribbean, young Hamilton notably wrote about what event?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "A fire that killed his family",
        choiceB: "A smallpox outbreak",
        choiceC: "A hurricane",
        choiceD: "A rebellion",
        correct: "C"
    },
    {   // QUESTION #3
        question: "What college did Alexander Hamilton actually attend?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Collge of New Jersey",
        choiceB: "Kings College",
        choiceC: "College of William & Mary",
        choiceD: "Never went to college",
        correct: "B"
    }, { // QUESTION #4
        question: "What was Hamilton's role in Washington's cabinet?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Secretary of War",
        choiceB: "Secretary of the Treasury",
        choiceC: "Vice President",
        choiceD: "Secretary of State",
        correct: "B"
    }, { // QUESTION #5
        question: "Hamilton, Madison, and John Jay wrote 85 essays called:",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "US Constitution",
        choiceB: "Declaration of Independence",
        choiceC: "Bill of Rights",
        choiceD: "Federalist Papers",
        correct: "D"
    }, { // QUESTION #6
        question: "What was Hamilton's role during the Quasi war?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Inspector General of the Army",
        choiceB: "Artillery captain",
        choiceC: "Was not alive during Quasi war",
        choiceD: "Diplomat in France",
        correct: "A"
    }, { // QUESTION #7
        question: "Hamilton led an army to supress which rebellion?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Shays Rebellion",
        choiceB: "Whiskey Rebellion",
	choiceC: "Teenage Rebellion",
        choiceD: "Fries's Rebellion",
        correct: "B"
    }, { // QUESTION #8
        question: "who's quote? 'O I have read his Heart in his wicked Eyes many a time. 
The very devil is in them. 
They are laciviousness itself, or I have no skill in Physiognomy.' ",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Elizabeth Hamilton",
        choiceB: "Thomas Jefferson",
        choiceC: "Abigail Adams",
        choiceD: "Aaron Burr",
        correct: "C"
    }, { // QUESTION #9
        question: "Where does the duel between Hamilton and Burr take place?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "New York, NY",
        choiceB: "International Waters",
        choiceC: "Weehawken, NJ",
        choiceD: "Lawn in front of The White House",
        correct: "C"
    }, { // QUESTION #10
        question: "What battle did Hamilton's horse get shot from under him?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Bunker Hill",
        choiceB: "Brandywine",
        choiceC: "Monmouth",
        choiceD: "Yorktown",
        correct: "C"
    }
];